<examples>
    <example>
        <user:input>
            Bears are at the door, did you leave the garbage out?
        </user:input>
        <score>4</score>
        <score_reasons>
            - BAD: The vocabulary table lacks proper Romanian diacritics and complete details.
            - BAD: The beginner explanation is overly verbose and doesn’t immediately show the key vocabulary.
            - BAD: Hints inadvertently provide verb conjugation details that should be discovered by the learner.
            - BAD: The sentence structure explanation is too detailed instead of a simple conceptual template.
        </score_reasons>
        <assistant:output>
        Let's break down the sentence into parts. Here’s a possible vocabulary table to get you started:
        | Romanian |  English   |
        |----------|------------|
        |  urs	   |   bear     |
        |  ușă	   |   door     |
        |  gunoi   |   garbage  |
        |  a fi	   |   to be    |
        |  a lăsa  |   to leave |

        Now, think about the sentence structure. We have two parts: "Bears are at the door" and "did you leave the garbage out?"
        For the first part, we use the verb "a fi" (to be) to indicate location.
        For the second part, consider the verb "a lăsa" (to leave) in the past tense.

        Here’s a conceptual sentence structure:

        [Location] [Subject] [Verb], [Object] [Verb-past]?

        Your turn! Can you try to complete the sentence using the vocabulary and structure provided?
        </assistant:output>
    </example>

    <example>
        <user:input>
            Bears are at the door, did you leave the garbage out?
        </user:input>
        <score>10</score>
        <score_reasons>
        - GOOD: Provides a clear vocabulary table with correct Romanian diacritics.
        - GOOD: Presents a conceptual sentence structure without revealing conjugation details.
        - GOOD: Clues are concise and encourage the learner to attempt an answer.
        </score_reasons>
        <assistant:output>
            Cheatsheet:
            | Word      | Romanian | Type |
            |-----------|----------|------|
            | bear      | urs      | Noun |
            | door      | ușă      | Noun |
            | garbage   | gunoi    | Noun |
            | to be     | a fi     | Verb |
            | to leave  | a lăsa   | Verb |

            Sentence structure:
            [Location] [Subject] [Verb], [Object] [Verb-past]?

            Considerations:

            The sentence has two parts: one stating a location and one asking about a past action.
            The first clause uses the verb "a fi" to indicate where something is.
            The second clause involves "a lăsa" in its past tense form.
            
            Next steps:

            Attempt to construct the sentence using the given vocabulary.
            Ask for hints on prepositions and verb conjugations if needed.
            Experiment with different sentence structures to express location and past action.
        </assistant:output>
    </example>
</examples>